A Finding Aid to the LeRoy Neiman Papers, 1938-2005, in the Archives of American Art AAA.neimlero
Archives of American Art
Sept. 1988 "New Perspectives on Contemporary Art," Tunnel Club, New York
Oct. 1988 "Women in Sports," Springfield College, Springfield, MA
Oct.-Nov. 1988 "Annual American Masters Exhibition," Foster Harmon Galleries of American Art, Sarasota, FL
Dec. 1988 "The Most Famous Artist Alive," Tunnel Club, New York
Jan. 1989 "Art's As Good An Investment as Bonds," Baja Club, New York
March 1989 "The Greatest Hits Vol 1 Show," Tunnel Club, New York
July-Aug. 1989 "20/20 Exhibition," Steiner& Young Galleries, Marietta, Georgia
June 1990 Amnesty International Exhibition, New York
Summer 1990 "Director's Choice," Park Shore Gallery, Naples, FL
Sept. 1991 "Expose Yourself to Art," University of Southern Florida
May 1-June 10, 1992 "Drawing New Conclusions," Art Institute of Chicago
1993 "Salon d'Automne," Grand Palais, Paris
1993 "Equine Art" Solo Exhibition, Kentucky Derby Museum
1995 "Racing Retrospective" Solo Exhibition, Kentucky Derby Museum
1994-1995 "Louis Armstrong: A Cultural Legacy," Queens Museum of Art, New York
June 14, 1996 Cig Art, National Arts Club Exhibition and Benefit
1996 "Portraits of Our Times 1946-96" Solo Exhibition and Catalog, Bowles/Sorokko/Yarger Galleries
Oct. 1998 "Animals: The Wild and the Tame" Solo Exhibition, Franklin Bowles Gallery, San Francisco
2001 "LeRoy Neiman - A Retrospective Exhibition of Works on Paper," Fairfield Gallery
2001 "LeRoy Neiman: Master Printmaker," Franklin Bowles Gallery, San Francisco
2002 "LeRoy Neiman: Thirty Years in San Francisco," Franklin Bowles Galleries, San Francisco
2003 "A View from the Table" Solo Exhibition, Hammer Galleries, New York
2005 "LeRoy Neiman: The Art of Boxing," Franklin Bowles Galleries
Appendix F: Index to Collection
A
ABC (American Broadcasting Company) - 2.2: ABC Correspondence, 4.1: 1977
ABC's Wide World of Sports - 4.1: 1987, see also Olympic Games
AIMS (Committee to Aid Multiple Sclerosis) - 4.1: 1977, 1978
ASPCA - 3.1: ASPCA 1986-1988
Aaron, Hank - 4.1: 1972
Abdul-Jabbar, Kareem - see Basketball Superstars, 1975-1976, and Johnson, Earvin Kareem Abdul-Jabbar, 1984 - 3.1: Kareem Abdul-Jabbar, 1984
Abramowitz, A.N. (Avie) - 2.2: A. N. Abramowitz 1974-1978, 3.2.1
Abrams, Harry N. - see 3.2 - Publications files, 4.1: 1999
Abrams, Judith Ann - 2.1: 1983, 1991
Absolut Vodka - see promotions
Academie Internationale des Arts Contemporains, Belgium - 2.1: 1992
accountant - see Jacobs, Jason
Adams, Joey - 1.1: Friars Club
Adamowski, Benjamin - 4.1: 1960
Addams, Charles - 4.1: 2000
Addison, Robert and Ruth (Betsy) - 2.1: 1978, 1990, 4.1: 1985, 1987, 1991 in two-person exhibition with LeRoy Neiman - 4.1: 1978 and ov
Advanced Materials and Processes Magazine - 4.1: 1989
Adventurer, between 1971 and 1977 - see Long, Captain Elgen
Adventuress, 1970s - see Earhart, Amelia
aerobics - 2.1: 1984, see also dance: Jacki Sorenson, 1981
Affronti, Judge Frank - 2.2: Judge Frank Affronti 1990-1999
Africa - see LeRoy Neiman On Safari
Afsary, Cyrus - 2.1: 1978
Air France - 4.2: Playboy 1963, see Appendix E
airlines
American Airlines - 2.1: 1999
Continental Airlines - see Fitzgerald, Ella
Albany, New York - 3.1: Tour de Trump
Alexander Hotel, Miami Beach - see promotions
Ali, Muhammad - see boxing
All - Sports Hall of Fame - 4.1: 1999
Allied Artists Council, Artists and Models Masque Ball, 1985 - 4.1: 1985
Allyson Louis Gallery - 2.1: 1988, 3.1: Morton's of Chicago 1982-present, 3.1: Superbowl XXII painting In the Pocket, at Allyson Louis Gallery 1988
Amahl and the Night Visitors, 1978 - 4.1: 1978
Amateur Athletic Association - 4.1: 1998
Amateur Athletic Union - 2.1: 1976
Ambassadors Hotel, East and West, Chicago - 3.1: Ambassadors 1960s, see also restaurants: The Pump Room
America's Cup - see sailing
American Academy of Achievement - see awards
American Beauty Association - 4.1: 1994
American Broadcasting Company - see ABC
American Cancer Society - 4.1: 1986, 1989, 1997, 2004
American Carnival, Japan - 4.1: 1988
American Diabetes Association - 4.1: 1990, see Appendix A
American Embassy, Nairobi, Kenya - 2.1: 1984
American Federation of Television and Radio Artists - 1.1: Name Tags and ID Cards
American Flag, 2002 - 3.1: Good Tidings Foundation 1998
American Fine Art Editions, Inc. - 4.1: 2004, see exhibitions
American Heart Association - 4.1: 1991
American in Paris, An - see LeRoy Neiman: An American in Paris
American Sport Art Museum - 2.1: 1989, 4.1: 1989
American Sportscasters Association - 1.1: Awards, 4.1: 1986; Hall of Fame Awards Dinner - 3.1: Long Term Projects
American Stock Exchange - see Stock Market
Amnesty International - see exhibitions, group: Blumhelman Gallery
Ampex Video Art - see television
Anderson, Dave - 4.1: 1983, see also Countdown to Superbowl by Dave Anderson
Anheuser-Busch - see promotions, 3.1: Duran vs. Leonard 1989
animals - see exhibitions, horse racing, 3.2.12
Animal Fair Magazine - 2.1: 2000, 4.1: 2000
Polar Bears - 4.1: 1979, 1984, 1993
birds - see also animals: roosters
Arkansas Wild Ducks, 1984 - 3.1: Arkansas Symphony Orchestra and Arkansas Wild Ducks, 1984
Fighting Cocks, Manila, 1976 drawing (watercolor) - 4.1: 1976
Manila Cock -Pit, 1976 drawing (watercolor) - 4.1: 1976
Parrots, 1982 - 4.1: 1984
Studies of Fighting Cocks, 1976 drawing (watercolor) - 4.1: 1976
cheetah
Kilimanjaro Cheetah, 1971 - 4.1: 1993
Portrait of the Cheetah, 2004 - 4.1: 2004
Cougar, 1981 painting and 1993 serigraph - 2.1: 1994, 4.1: 1993
cow - see Cow Parade
dog - 4.1: 1998
Black Labrador, 1977 - 4.1: undated 1990s
Borzoi - see also Pelkey, Joe (serigraph)
dog walkers - VC: 1983
The Great Dane, Hamlet, 1986 - 3.1: ASPCA 1986-1988, 4.1: 1986
Hounds of Chantilly - 2.1: 1980, 4.2: Playboy 1964, see Appendix E
Moore County Hounds, Southern Pines, North Carolina - 4.1: 1959, 4.2: Playboy 1960, see Appendix E
eagle, American Bald Eagle, 1978 - 4.1: 1993
elephant
Elephant Charge, 1999 - 4.1: 1999
Elephant Nocturne - 4.1: 1984, 1993
Elephant Stampede - 3.1: Advertising Layouts 1980s, 4.1: 1976, 1989, 1993, 1995 Shikar, 1980 - 4.1: 1982, 1993
giraffe, Giraffe Family - 4.1: 1978, 1993
gorilla, Gorilla Family - 4.1: 1993
horse - see horses
jaguar, Jaguar Family, 1984 - 4.1: 1993
leopard
Kenya Leopard, 1978 - 4.1: 1993
Leopard, 1971 serigraph - 3.1: Circle Gallery 1972, 4.1: 1988 -89, 1993
Serengeti Leopard, 1976 - 4.1: 1993
lion
Lion, 1968 - 4.1: 1993
Lions, date? - 4.1: 1974
Lion Couple - IV: 1984, 1993
Lion Family, 1974 - 2.1: 2004, 4.1: 1993
Lion's Pride II, 1978 - 4.1: 1993
Portrait of the Lion, 2002 - 4.1: 2002
Ocelot - 4.1: 1993
panther, Black Panther, 1975 - 3.1: Hammer Galleries Solo Exhibition 1975 -76, 4.1: 1975
rescue - see ASPCA, Bide-A-Wee, PAWS/LA, Humane Society of New York, Mount Pleasant Animal Shelter
rooster - Studies of Fighting Cocks, 1975 watercolor - 3.1: Hammer Galleries Solo Exhibition 1975-76
safari - 3.1: "LeRoy Neiman on Safari," The Wildlife Experience, Parker, CO, 2003, 3.2.12
tiger
Bengal Tiger - 4.1: 1993
Caspian Tiger, 1985 - 4.1: 1993
Delacroix's Tiger - 4.1: undated, 1993
Tiger, 1985 - 4.1: 1993
Young Tiger - 4.1: 1993
unicorn
The Hunt of The Unicorn, late 1960s mural - 3.1: "The Playboy Collection," Dyansen Gallery Traveling Exhibition 1989-90, 4.2: Playboy Ephemera 1960s
whale - see Moby Dick
wolf - see Call of the Wild, 1993
zebra, Zebra Family - 3.1: The Art Exchange Solo Exhibitions, Creve Coeur, MO 1978-79, 4.1: 1984, 1993
zoo - 3.2.12d
Anisfeld, Boris - 2.1: 1988
Anthony, Earl - see bowling
Antonacci, Joe - 4.1: 1982
Apollo Theater - 4.1: undated 1990s, 1998
Area nightclub, New York - 3.1: "Art", Group Exhibition at Area, 1985
arenas - see The Spectrum, Madison Square Garden
Arizona Heart Institute - see The Open Heart, 1982
Arizona Landscape, 1979 - 2.1: 1979
Arkansas - 3.1: Arkansas Symphony Orchestra and Arkansas Wild Ducks, 1984
Arledge, Roone - 2.2: ABC Correspondence, 3.1: Olympics Munich 1972, 3.1: "Recent Graphics and Drawings," The Far Gallery Solo Exhibition 1971, 3.1: Olympics, Montreal 1976 Roone Arledge, 1972 drawing - 4.1: 2003
Arliss - 4.1: 1996
Armory Art Fair, Washington DC - 4.1: 1977
Armstrong, Louis - see jazz
Army, U.S., service in - 1.1: Military Service
Army vs. Navy 1946, 2000 - 4.1: 2001
Arnstein, Vera Daphne - 4.1: 1990
Arrow shirts - see promotions
Art Aid - 4.1: 1986
L'art et l'automobile - 3.1: LeRoy Neiman Corvette 1984, 4.1: 1988, 2002, see also exhibitions
Art Brokerage Inc. - see Rose, Donna
Art Collection House Co., Ltd., Japan - 2.1: 1994, 1995
Art Directors Club of Oklahoma City - 4.1: 1967, VII
Art Expo - 4.1: Undated
Art for Education - 4.1: 1998
The Art of Gaming Through the Ages, by Arthur Flowers and Anthony Curtis, foreword by LeRoy Neiman - 3.1: The Art of Gaming Through the Ages, Huntington Press, 2000
Art Institute of Boston - 1.1: Honorary Degrees, 2.1: 1975, 4.1: 1975
Art Institute of Chicago - 1.1: Education and Teaching, 2.1: 1987, 1989, 1996, 3.1: "Drawing New Conclusions," Art Institute of Chicago group exhibition 1992, 4.1: 1978 ov, 2001, 2002, see also exhibitions
Auxiliary Board - 2.1: 1990
Barewalls, 2001 - 3.1: Art Institute of Chicago Reunion 2001
Art and Lifestyle, 1974 - see LeRoy Neiman: Art and LifeStyle, 1974, 3.2.1
ArtExpo New York - 2.1: 1989, 4.1: 1987, 1998, 2001
Art-o-gram: News of the art world for art dealers only - 4.1: 1977
Arthur Andersen & Co. - 4.1: 1981
Les Arts de France - 2.1: 1988
Arum, Bob and Lovee - 2.1: 1996, 1998, 4.1: 1996
Ascent, 1961 - 4.1: 1961
Ashford, Evelyn - see running
Aspen, CO - 4.1: 1993, 1994
Association for the Help of Retarded Children (AHRC) - 3.1: Thurman Munson and Thurman Munson Awards Dinner 1977-present
Astaire, Fred
Fred Astaire - 3.1: Good Tidings Foundation 1998 -, 4.1: 1985
Athens International Festival - 4.1: 1993
Atlanta, GA - 3.1: Economic Opportunity Atlanta 1968
Atlanta International Film Festival - 4.1: 1974 and ov, V: 1974
Atlanta Magazine - 4.1: 1969, 1975, 1996
Atlanta's Poor People Art School - 4.1: 1969
Atlantic City, New Jersey - see also casinos, promotions, 3.1: Tour de Trump 1989
attorney - see Shaw, Robert
auction - 4.1: 1978, 1997, 1998, 1999
Augusta National Golf Club, The 16th at Augusta, 1992 - 4.1: 1994
auto racing - 4.1: 1982, 1983, 1989, 1999
Andretti, Mario - 4.1: 1975, 1992
Andretti, Michael - 4.1: 1992
Brayton, Scott - 4.1: 1996
Beni Hana Grand Prix - 2.1: 1978
Caesar's Palace Grand Prix, 1981 - 3.1: Caesar's Palace Grand Prix 1981-83
Caesar's Palace Grand Prix, 1982 - 3.1: Caesar's Palace Grand Prix 1981-83
Caesar's Palace Grand Prix, 1983 - 3.1: Caesar's Palace Grand Prix 1981-83
Can-Am Race - 4.2: Playboy 1970, see Appendix E
Dallas Grand Prix, 1984 - 2.2: Neiman-Marcus 1983-88, 3.1: Dallas Grand Prix 1984
Denver Grand Prix, 1990 - 3.1: Denver Grand Prix 1990-1991
Denver Grand Prix, 1991 - 3.1: Denver Grand Prix 1990-1991
Ferrari - 4.1: 1989
Fittipaldi, Emerson
Fittipaldi, 1989 - 3.1: Emerson Fittipaldi 1989, 4.1: 1990
Grand Prix Heart Ball - 3.1: Denver Grand Prix 1990-91
Grand Prix de Monaco - 2.1: 1986, 2.2: Playboy Enterprises Inc. 1980s, 4.2: Playboy Ephemera 1980, Press and Paraphernalia
Grand Prix de Monaco, 1976 - 4.1: 1993, 4.2: Playboy Ephemera 1980, Press and Paraphernalia
Indianapolis 500 - 3.1: Indy 500, 1985-87
Pits at Indy, 1968 - 2.1: 1976
Le Mans - 3.2. Winners, 1983, Harry N. Abrams Notes on Auto Racing and Basketball, 4.2: Playboy 1969, 4.2: Playboy Ephemera 2000s, see Appendix E
Miami Grand Prix - 3.1: Miami Grand Prix 1991-92
Toyota Grand Prix of Miami, 1991 (for 1992 race) - 3.1: Miami Grand Prix 1991-92
Penske, Roger - 3.1: Indy 500, 1985-87
Revson, Peter
Peter Revson, Can-Am Race, 1970 drawing - 3.1: Rotonda Superstars 1973-75
Toyota Monterey Grand Prix, 1990 - 4.1: 1990
Laguna Seca Raceway, 1989 - 4.1: 1990
automobiles - 3.1: LeRoy Neiman Corvette 1984, 4.1: 1993, 1999, 2001, see also l'Art et l'Automobile, and auto racing
The Robb Report Magazine - 2.1: 1982, 4.1: 1983, 1987
Rolls-Royce - 3.1: Lawrence Ross Galleries Exhibitions 1985, 4.1: undated, 1983
awards - 1.1: Awards
B
Baden Baden - 2.1: 1997
Baghdad of the Midwest, 1975 - see Saint Paul, Minnesota
Bailey, Jim - see golf: Atlanta National Golf Club
Baker, Dusty - 4.1: 1998
Bal de la Mer - 3.1: Monaco 1994, 4.1: 1994
Baldwin, James, James Baldwin, 1961 and 1964 drawings - 2.1: 2002
ballet - 4.1: 1987, V: Kathy Healey, 1981, see also dance
Ballet Arkansas - 2.1: 1990, 4.1: undated 1980s
Ballet: The Daring Project, Joyce Theater, 1996 - 4.1: 1996
Ballet Theater Foundation, Inc. - 4.1: 1976
Baryshnikov, Mikhail, Baryshnikov, 1983 - 3.1: Des Moines Ballet Commissions 1983-1986, 3.2. Winners, 1983, Harry N. Abrams
Bolshoi Ballet - 4.1: 1968, 4.2: Playboy 1969
Gregory, Cynthia - 2.1: 1986, 2.1: 1990
Nureyev, Rudolph, Nureyev, 1974 drawing - 3.1: Hammer Galleries Solo Exhibition 1975-76, Nureyev, 1986 - 3.1: Des Moines Ballet Commissions 1983-1986
Prima Ballerina 'Assoluta' - 2.1: 1986, 1989, 4.1: 1989
Ballot, Isabelle - 4.1: 1996, 1998, 2001
Barber, Tiki - 4.1: 2001, 2002
Barclays Bank - 4.1: 1993
Bardot, Brigitte - 4.1: 1961
BareWalls - 1.1: Education and Teaching-Art Institute of Chicago after 1959
Barkley, Charles - 4.1: 1999, 2001, V: Photographs
Charles Barkley, 1997 - V: Photographs
Barnet, Will - 2.2: JoAnn Perse Gallery 1983-02
Barnett, Dick - 4.1: 1990
"Baroque Bravura Today?" undated article by LeRoy Neiman - 4.1: undated
Barrington Enterprises Inc. - see Landau, Barry
bars - see restaurants and bars
Bartender Magazine - 2.2: Bartender Magazine, 4.2: Bartender Magazine
Ultimate Cocktail Book, 1990 - 4.2: Bartender Magazine
Ultimate Cocktail Book II - 4.2: Bartender Magazine
Baryshnikov, Mikhail - see ballet
baseball - 3.1: Mickey Mantle 1962-99, 3.1: Leo Durocher 1974 -1994, 3.1: Rusty Staub 1975 -1994, 3.1: Gaylord Perry's 300th win, 3.1: Willie Stargell 1980, 3.1: Nolan Ryan, 1981, 3.1: Skoal Pinch Hitter 1985 -87, 3.1: Dodgers Centennial, 3.1: The Shot Heard 'Round the World, 1991, 3.1: Phil Rizzuto 1994, 3.1: Casey Stengel 1996, 3.1: Jackie Robinson, 1997, 3.1: Mike Piazza 1999, 3.2.13, 4.1: 1992, also search for individual players and coaches by name in Index and Appendix A
All-Stars - 4.1: undated
Baseball Players, 1983 - 4.1: 1983
Baseball Writers Association of America - 4.1: 1990, 1993
Bay Area Baseball, 1990 - 3.1: Bay Area Baseball debut at Bowles/Sorokko, San Francisco 1990, 4.1: 1991
Boston Red Sox - 4.1: 1975, 1982, 1986
Brooklyn Dodgers - 3.1: The Shot Heard 'Round the World, 1991, 3.1: Jackie Robinson, 1997, see also Los Angeles Dodgers
Chicago Cubs - 3.1: Leo Durocher 1974-94, 3.1: Skoal Pinch Hitter Thad Bosley 1985
Cincinnati Reds - 4.1: 1975, 1986
Cleveland Indians - 4.1: 1975
etchings - 3.1: Circle Gallery 1972
Florida Marlins, 1992 - 2.1: 1992, 4.1: 1992
Hollywood All-Stars - 3.1: Mickey Mantle Paintings 1962-1999
Home Run Blast, 2002 etching - 3.2.13
Japan - 3.1: Hawaii and Japan 1974
Kansas City Royals - 4.1: 1990
Los Angeles Dodgers - 2.1: 1992, 3.1: Jackie Robinson, 1997, 4.1: 1992; Dodgers Centennial, 1990 - 3.1: Dodgers Centennial 1990, 4.1: 1991
National Baseball Hall of Fame and Museum, Cooperstown, NY - 2.1: 1978, 1996, 3.1: Leo Durocher 1974-94, 3.1: Phil Rizzuto 1994, 3.1: Casey Stengel 1996, 4.1: 1990, 1993 (yearbook), 1994, 1995
New York Giants - 3.1: The Shot Heard 'Round the World, 1991
New York Mets - 3.1: Rusty Staub 1975-1994, 3.1: Casey Stengel 1996, 4.1: 1979, 1985, 1986, 1990, 1991, 1996, 2001, 2002
New York Yankees - 2.1: 2004, 3.1: Mickey Mantle 1962-99, 3.1: Phil Rizzuto 1994, 4.1: 1977, 2000
Oakland Athletics - 2.1: 1993, 4.1: 1988 -89, 1993
Oklahoma Redhawks (minor league) - 2.1: 1998
Philadelphia Phillies - 4.1: 1993
Pittsburgh Pirates - 3.1: Willie Stargell 1980, 4.1: 1984; Pittsburgh Pirates, 1973 - 4.1: 1973
Saint Louis Cardinals - 4.1: 1999
San Francisco Giants - 4.1: 1988-89
Seattle Mariners - 3.1: Gaylord Perry's 300th Win file
Sliding Home, serigraph - 3.1: Circle Gallery 1972, 4.1: 1978, 1988, 1989; team yearbooks - 3.1: Dodgers Centennial 1990, 4.1: 1973, 1977, 1979, 2001
World Series: 1966 - VII; 1972 - 4.1: 1972; 1975 - 4.1: 1975, 1986; 1976 - 2.1: 1976; 1986 - 4.1: 1986; 1989 - 4.1: 1989
basketball
Basketball, 1972 - 4.1: 1992
Basketball Superstars, 1975-76 - 4.1: 1977, 2001
college basketball - 4.1: 1992, 1994
Indiana University Hoosiers; Hoosier Hoopla, 1975 - 2.1: 1975, 4.1: 1976, 1978, 1989, VII: Pendants
North Carolina Tar Heels - 4.1: 1977
Oregon State University - 4.1: 1977
University of Kentucky Wildcats; The Wildcats, 1978 - 3.1: The Wildcats 1978
University of Nevada, Las Vegas - 4.1: 1983
Naismith Memorial Basketball Hall of Fame - 3.1: Naismith Memorial Basketball Hall of Fame 1978-91
NBA basketball - 3.1: Kareem Abdul-Jabbar, 1984, 3.1: Orlando Magic commission, 1990, 3.1: Larry Bird, 1993, 4.1: 1977, 1979
All-Stars - 4.1: 1977
NBA All -Star Game - 4.1: 1978
Boston Celtics - 3.1: Larry Bird, 1993, 4.1: 1989 ov
Buffalo Braves - 2.1: 1976
Chicago Bulls - 4.1: 1989
Houston Rockets - 4.1: 1975
Los Angeles Clippers - 2.1: 1989
Los Angeles Lakers - 3.1: Kareem Abdul-Jabbar, 1984, 4.1: 1989 ov
Milwaukee Bucks - 4.1: 1977
New York Knicks - 4.1: 1968, 1969, 1974, 1976, 1980, 1989, 1993
Orlando Magic - 3.1: Orlando Magic commission 1990, 4.1: 1989
Philadelphia 76ers - 4.1: 1999
Washington Bullets - 4.1: 1980
Battig, Joseph - 2.1: 1996
Battle of the Bay, serigraph - 4.1: 1989
Baumgartner, Bruce - see wrestling
Beard, James - 3.1: James Beard 1985-2002, 4.1: 1996
The Beatles
The Beatles, 1966, serigraph 1992 - 3.1: Dyansen Gallery Solo Exhibition, Atlantic City, and The Beatles serigraph 1992
John Lennon, 1990 etching - 3.1: John Lennon Etching 1990
Beatty, Warren - 3.1: Tyson vs. Spinks 1988
beauty pageants
ITMSA Miss Legs Competition - 2.1: 1983
Miss America - 3.1: Miss America Pageant 1983-1984
Miss Asia - 3.1: Miss Asia Pageant 1986
Miss J.A.P. and Miss Purim Pageants - 4.1: 1982
Miss Legs America - 2.1: 1980, 4.1: 1984
Miss Teen USA - 3.1: Miss Teen USA Pageant 1983
Miss Universe - 3.1: Miss Universe Pageant 1981
Miss USA - 3.1: Miss USA Pageant 1978
Miss World -USA - 3.1: Miss World-USA Beauty Pageant 1975
Mrs. America - 3.1: Mrs. America Pageant 1982
Playboy Bunny of the Year Pageant - 2.2: Playboy Enterprises Inc. 1970s
Beaux Arts, Inc. Award - 1.1: Awards
Begin, Menachem - 3.1: Peace Treaty, 1980
Behan, Brendan - see Borstal Boy
Behm, Kenneth - 2.1: 1989
Bench, Johnny - 4.1: 1972
Bench, The Catcher, 1989 - 3.1: Johnny Bench 1989
Bennett, Chef John - 2.2: Chef John Bennett 1998 -2000, 4.1: 2002, John Bennett, 1988 drawing - 4.1: 1988, 1998
Bennett, Tony - 4.1: 1963, 1973, 1985
Berra, Yogi - 4.1: 1985, 1998
Yogi Berra Museum - 3.1: "Viva el Beisbol!" exhibition, Yogi Berra Museum, 2000
Bernstein, Leonard, Leonard Bernstein, 1972 - 4.1: 1972; Leonard Bernstein, undated drawing - 4.1: 1972; Leonard Bernstein, 1967 drawing - 4.1: 1998
Bethany College - 4.1: 1979
Bethesda Fountain; View of Bethesda Fountain, 1989 - 3.1: A Salute to Central Park Exhibition 1989
Better Boys Foundation - 4.1: 1974
Beverly Hills, California - 2.1: 1985, 1989, see exhibitions: Lawrence Ross Galleries
Beverly Hills Hotel - 2.1: 1989
Bide-A-Wee - 4.1: 1992
Big Time Golf, by LeRoy Neiman - 3.1: Saks Fifth Avenue 1994-1999, 3.2:10
billboard - 3.1: Stadium Tennis Billboard, 1981, 3.1: Caesar's Palace Grand Prix 1981-83, 3.1: Folies Bergere, Tropicana, Las Vegas 1983, VC: 1980s
Billboard Magazine International Billie Awards - 3.1: Billboard Magazine First Annual Billie Awards 1993
billiards - 4.2: Billiard World Magazine 1963-65
Billiard World Magazine - 4.2: Billiard World Magazine 1963-65
Pool Game, 1966 - 4.1: 1998
Pool Room, serigraph - 3.1: Circle Gallery 1972
Sardi's World Billiard Championship - 4.2: Playboy 1963, see Appendix E
Bimini, Bahamas - 2.1: 1977, 1979
Bingo, 1973 - 4.1: 1989
Binns, James - 4.1: 1996, 2000
Bird, Larry, Larry Bird, 1992 - 3.1: Larry Bird, 1993, see also Johnson, Earvin "Magic": Magic
birthday - 4.1: 1999
Black Labrador, 1977 - see animals
Black Panther, 1975 - see animals
Blackwood, Glenn - 4.1: 1993
Bland, Bobby Blue - 3.1: Blues Ball 1997-2004
Blaukmer, Professor Frederika - 4.1: 1979
Blecker, Tom, Kathy, and Barbra - 2.2: Artwork by Children, 2.2: Tom Blecker 1989-99
Bloomberg, Mayor Michael - 1.1: New York Friars Club, 1990s-2000s
Blue Moon Bay Co., Ltd., Japan - 2.1: 1997
bloopers - 4.1: 1978, 1997
Bluebird Café - 3.1: Iroquois Steeplechase, Nashville, TN, 1993
Blues Ball - 3.1: Blues Ball 1997-2004
Blum's - 3.1: Early Fashion Illustration 1949-57
B'nai B'rith - 1.1: Awards
Boathouse Restaurant - see Central Park Boathouse
boats - see sailing, or Showboats International; The Cambridge-Oxford Boat Race - 4.2: Playboy 1962, see Appendix E
Bochette, Liston - 2.1: 1981, 1984, 1985
bodybuilding - 4.1: 1977, 1982, 1990
Everson, Cory - 4.1: 1990
Schwarzenegger, Arnold - see Schwarzenegger, Arnold
Boek, Louis - 1.1: Military Service
Boggs, Bill - 4.1: 2002 ov., 2004
Bonaventure - see St. Bonaventure University
Bond, Julian - 4.1: 1969
Bonds, Barry - Barry Bonds, 2003 pastel - 3.1: Good Tidings Foundation, 1998-present book jacket illustrations - 3.1: folder 1, 3.1: Charlotte Chandler 1978-84, 4.1: 1973, 1982, 1988-89
Book of the Month Club - 3.2.5, 3.2. Winners, 1983, Harry N. Abrams, Text Drafts
books
by Mr. Neiman - see Publications files in Series 3.2
by others, containing Mr. Neiman's works - see Licensing Art and Design by Cynthia Revelli, Skip Singleton tennis books, see also book jacket illustrations
bookstores - see Publications files in series 3.2 for information on book signings at bookstores
Borg, Bjorn - see tennis
Borstal Boy - 2.1: 1984, 3.1: Borstal Boy 1970
Bosley, Thad - see Skoal Pinch Hitter
Bourgeois, Louise - 3.1: "Cig Art" Benefit Exhibitions 1996-2000
Bourne, Bob - 4.1: 1983
Bowe, Riddick - see boxing
Bowlers Journal - see bowling
Bowles, Franklin - see Bowles Galleries
Bowles Galleries - 1.2: Bowles Galleries, see exhibitions, see also Timothy Yarger Fine Art
bowling - 2.1: 1976
Anthony, Earl - 3.1: Million Dollar Strike, 1982
Carter, Don - 3.1: Million Dollar Strike, 1982
Esposito, Frank - 2.1: 1986, 1996, 3.1: Million Dollar Strike, 1982
Million Dollar Strike, 1982 - 3.1: Million Dollar Strike, 1982
Varipapa, Andy - 3.1: Million Dollar Strike, 1982
boxing - 3.1: Ali vs. Frazier I, 1971, 3.1: Ali vs. Frazier III "The Thrilla in Manila," 1975, 3.1: Ali vs. Spinks 1978, 3.1: Sportsman's Ball 1978, 3.1: Ali vs. Holmes 1980, 3.1: Duran vs. Leonard I, II, III 1980-89, 3.1: Hearns vs. Leonard 1981, 3.1: Tribute to Joe Louis (Holmes vs. Spinks) 1981, 3.1: Holmes vs. Cooney 1982, 3.1: Hagler vs. Hearns 1985, 3.1: Mike Tyson Portraits 1986-1990s, 3.1: Tyson vs. Spinks 1988, 3.1: McGirt vs. Whitaker 1993, 3.1: Tyson vs. Holyfield 1991-1996, 3.1: Holyfield -Lewis and Ali vs. Frazier I, 1971, 1999, 3.1: Lewis vs. Tyson 2002, 3.1: De La Hoya vs. Vargas 2002, 4.1: 1964, 1965, 1966, 1967, 1970, 1971, 1972, 1976, 1977, 1978, 1979, 1981, 1982, 1983, 1984, 1985, 1987, 1988, 1989, undated 1990s, 1990, 1991, 1993, 1994, 1995, 1996, 1997, 1998, 1999, 2000, 2001, 2002
Ali, Muhammad - see Ali vs. Frazier, 3.1: Lewis vs. Tyson 2002, .2.1: 2001, 3.1: GOAT (Greatest of All Time - A Tribute to Muhammad Ali) Book by Taschen, 2004, 3.2.1, 3.2.16, 4.1: 1964, 1965, 1966, 1967, 1970, 1971, 1974, 1976, 1977, 1978, 1980, 1985 1991, 1994, 1995, 1997, 1998, 1999, 2000, 2001, 4.2: Playboy Ephemera 1960s, 4.2: The Ring Magazine as artist - 2.1: 1979, 4.1: 1966, 1967, 1970 ov, 1979
Muhammad Ali - Athlete of the Century, 2000 - 3.1: Muhammad Ali - Athlete of the Century, 2000-2002
Muhammad Ali - The Greatest Collector's Edition Magazine, 2002 - 4.1: 2002
Ali vs. Foreman, Zaire poster, 1974 - 4.1: 1974, 2000, 2002
Ali vs. Frazier
Ali vs. Frazier I, 1971 - 3.1: Ali vs. Frazier I, 1971
Ali vs. Frazier I, 1971, 1999 - 3.1: Holyfield -Lewis and Ali vs. Frazier I, 1999, 4.1: 2000